University of California, Los Angeles. Office of the Assistant Vice Chancellor for Business records UARC.0458
UCLA Library Special Collections
- Series 4: Administrative files, 1960-1990
  - Intercollegiate Athletics: budgets and income, 1984-1986 (Box 55, Folder 4)
  - Interface with Treasurer's Office, 1981 (Box 57, Folder 9)
  - International Association of Universities Meeting at UCLA, 1981-1982 (Box 71, Folder 1)
  - International House feasibility study and planning, 1980-1982 (Box 71, Folder 2-3)
  - Interview with Harlan Thompson, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Japanese Gardens, 1978-1979 (Box 71, Folder 4)
  - KCET/UCLA collaboration, 1982 (Box 71, Folder 5-6)
  - Lamson (Baldwin G.) residence rental, 1980-1982 (Box 71, Folder 7)
  - Laundry facilities study, 1960-1984 (Box 73, Folder 1-3)
  - Long Range Development Plan (LRDP), 1979-1990 (Box 73, Folder 4-5, Box 74, Folder 1-4)
    Includes property acquisition, transportation and parking services, building and development plans, building additions and housing construction, facilities, and off-campus sites.
  - LRDP: Environmental Impact Report, 1990 (Box 74, Folder 5-6, Box 75, Folder 1)
  - LRDP: general, 1988 (Box 75, Folder 2)
  - LRDP: Campus Construction Impact Committee, 1985-1989 (Box 75, Folder 3)
  - LRDP: Northwest Campus Site and Massing Study, 1985 (Box 75, Folder 4)
  - LRDP: Northwest Campus Development Plan, 1985-1988 (Box 76, Folder 1-5)
  - LRDP: North Westwood Village Development Plan, 1981-1987 (Box 77, Folder 1-3)
  - LRDP: South Campus Study, 1985-1986 (Box 77, Folder 4)
  - LRDP: Transportation Analysis, 1990 (Box 77, Folder 5)
  - LRDP: West Campus Development Plan, 1984-1986 (Box 77, Folder 6, Box 78, Folder 1-2)
  - LRDP: West Campus Development Plan Coordinating Committee, 1986-1987 (Box 78, Folder 3)
  - LRDP: West Campus Development Plan- Office Facilities Planning Task Force, 1986 (Box 78, Folder 4)
  - LRDP: West Campus Development Plan- Science and Technology Plaza, 1983-1986 (Box 78, Folder 5)
  - LRDP: West Medical Campus, 1980 (Box 78, Folder 6)
  - LRDP: Westwood Horizons building, 1980 (Box 78, Folder 7)
  - LRDP: Westwood Park parking structure, 1987-1989 (Box 79, Folder 1-2)
  - Lot 1 Mixed Use Medical Facilities Complex Project, 1986 (Box 79, Folder 3)
  - Medical Center: finances and strategic planning, 1976-1986 (Box 55, Folder 5)
  - Management Effectiveness Program- Business Operations Division, 1975-1978 (Box 79, Folder 4)
  - Systemwide Leadership: The Report of the President's Task Force on The Systemwide Administration of the University of California, 1977 (Box 79, Folder 5)
  - Murphy Hall space planning, 1977-1978 (Box 80, Folder 1-2)
  - Newspaper vending on campus, 1978-1979 (Box 80, Folder 3)
  - 1984 Olympics planning, 1977-1985 (Box 80, Folder 4-7, Box 81)
    Includes transportation services and parking structures, staffing, financial planning, site construction, campus hosting, and other aspects of planning.
  - 1984 Olympics operations organization plan, 1980 (Box 82, Folder 1)
  - LA Olympics Organizing Committee (LAOOC) administrative offices at UCLA, 1980-1984 (Box 82, Folder 2)
  - LA Olympics Organizing Committee (LAOOC) agreement with UCLA, 1979-1984 (Box 82, Folder 3-6)
  - 1984 Olympics Arts Festival: agreement between LAOOC and UCLA, 1983 (Box 82, Folder 7)
  - 1984 Olympics: parking, traffic, and transportation plans, 1982-1984 (Box 83, Folder 1-5)
  - Organization charts, 1968-1974 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Organization and functions manual, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Planning Office: annual space assignments inventories, 1981-1984 (Box 55, Folder 6)
  - Productivity measurement, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Productivity Measurement Program: Business Operations Division, 1978-1981 (Box 83, Folder 6, Box 62, Folder 1)
  - Reorganization of Business Operations Division, 1973-1987 (Box 62, Folder 2-8)
  - Royce Hall renovation and John Wooden Center planning, 1979-1986 (Box 62, Folder 9, Box 63, Folder 1)
  - Seismic Anchoring Manual, 1989 (Box 63, Folder 2)
  - Service Enterprises Finance and Working Capital fund, 1977-1978 (Box 63, Folder 3-4)
  - Space Analysis Report: Business Operations Division, 1981 (Box 63, Folder 5)
  - Staff personnel, 1978-1988 (Box 56, Folder 6)
  - Systemwide Business Affairs Program Review: reports and correspondence, 1977 (Box 58, Folder 5-6)
  - Tax exemption policy for university-leased properties, 1976-1980 (Box 67, Folder 1)
  - Tennis Stadium project planning, 1980-1981 (Box 67, Folder 2)
  - Terasaki Tissue Typing Laboratory: leasing of facilities by university, 1974-1977 (Box 67, Folder 3)
  - Transition planning: James Hobson retirement, 1990 (Box 67, Folder 4)
  - UCLA Foundation, 1975-1977 (Box 67, Folder 5)
  - Uniform policy, 1976-1978 (Box 67, Folder 6)
  - Unrelated business income filing for university, 1972, 1973-1983 (Box 67, Folder 7)
  - US-Asia Institute, "Partners In Progress" application by UCLA, 1982 (Box 55, Folder 3)
  - Visitors Center facility planning, 1979-1980 (Box 67, Folder 8)
  - Working capital, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 6)